question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
        "question": "In Chobits, Hideki found Chii in his apartment.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
        "question": "The name of the attack &quot;Kamehameha&quot; in Dragon Ball Z was named after a famous king of Hawaii.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
        "question": "In the &quot;Toaru Kagaku no Railgun&quot; anime,  espers can only reach a maximum of level 6 in their abilities.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Gosho Aoyama Made This Series: (Detective Conan \/ Case Closed!)", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Kiznaiver is an adaptation of a manga.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {
        "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga", "question": "Clefairy was intended to be Ash&#039;s starting Pok&eacute;mon in the pilot episode of the cartoon.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
        "question": "Studio Ghibli is a Japanese animation studio responsible for the films &quot;Wolf Children&quot; and &quot;The Boy and the Beast&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
        "question": "The anime &quot;Lucky Star&quot; follows the story of one girl who is unaware she is God.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
        "question": "In the 1988 film &quot;Akira&quot;, Tetsuo ends up destroying Tokyo.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
        "question": "In Kill La Kill, the weapon of the main protagonist is a katana. ", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
